When imagining your own site, imagine the site has this functionality:
Its purpose is to help the user test their knowledge of a topic they choose. 
The user will be able to enter a question, and its associated answers. 
How many ways can somebody create a question? 
Single Choice.. Multiple Choice.. What else?
The questions can be categorized in some way. 
Keywords would be a way of putting a question in a given category.
The user can search for questions that fall in a given category, and get an exam based on those questions.